I just wanna, I just wanna, I just wanna run, run, run around, run around, run, run around
I just wanna, I just wanna, I just wanna run, run, run around, run, run around
I just wanna run, run, run around, run around, run around, run around I'm Rio Kitagawa, 23.
I'm Hamari Okumura.
I'm Mei this month.
I'm in the middle of a group photo shoot for Bochi-san right now,
To make the most of my free time, I'd like to introduce the contents of Bochi.
Yay!
Then, let's get Bochi out.
Deden!
Then, let me explain.
It's a backpack that came with me, like a smaller version of the backpack I used in elementary school,
I found it when I was cleaning out the house, so I tried it out,
I found it when I was cleaning out the house. I thought it was great because it held a lot of stuff, had compartments, and pockets,
I use it when I'm at home.
I use it when I'm at home. It's nice.
This is a pouch that came with last year's COSME DECORTE Christmas coffret,
It's cute and holds a lot. Unexpectedly.
That's why I love using it.
It's cute.
Yes, I'm the only one with a My Mel-chan pouch,
It's a vanity pouch, so it's really like the perfect cosmetic storage,
It opens ridiculously, and it's nice.
It's so cute.
So cute.
Okay, so I brought three cosmetics for each of you.
The first one.
It's KOSE's Curl Keep Magic.
I happened to find this mascara and bought it.
My eyelashes go up so much.
I always use it at live performances.
I can do well with just this.
Isn't Oda-san a fan of this too?
I'm sure he does.
I thought it was really good, so please use it.
It's great. I used to love it too.
Mascara is very important.
I'll leave you with this one.
It's really big.
It's a primer called "Cream Inlay" from Kanemo,
I had a really bad problem with my mask crumbling, so I put this on and it never crumbles,
It doesn't dry out, but it doesn't break up, and it's very moisturizing,
It doesn't dry out, but it also doesn't fall apart,
I really want to go to my grave with this in my arms,
It's the kind of cosmetic that I want to use for the rest of my life.
By the way, I have one too.
I have the tube type.
I am a believer.
A believer.
I would like to introduce the first one to you.
This is it.
Till Till's Mask Fit Essence.
I've been curious about it.
This is so good, I quite like and collect primers and cosmetics,
What can I say about this one? Even if I just apply this, it tones up my skin,
It also fills in my pores, but I don't feel like I'm wearing it,
I think this primer works best when used in combination with the Till Till foundation.
There are two kinds.
Two kinds.
I'm curious. I'm interested in it. It's really good.
This one is really nice too.
When I perform live, I do all of my own makeup, even my hair. I do a lot of TV taping, and when I perform on a big stage for the final leg of a tour, I often have a makeup artist come in, but I definitely do my eyelashes by myself.
I leave everything to them.
I am also very particular about my base makeup, so I often have my own makeup artist use it.
But we don't do most of our own makeup.
That's right. So we share a lot of information with each other, and we often tell each other things like, "This cosmetic was really good," or "I think this would look good on you.
Second.
Yes. This is Suzanne's Pearl Brow Highlight.
This was given to me by Hamari Okamura,
It gives a really nice shine,
It is said to be a highlighter that gives a wet and shiny look.
It's very shiny and I used it on my tear ducts.
It's cute.
It looks much better. It's so pretty.
And now, on to the next one.
Then, next, I used various work stage eye palettes,
There are so many different colors available,
I've been wearing a lot of gray makeup lately,
But this one has a lot of pink in it,
There are also delicate lamé shades,
It also contains an eye shadow base.
Just by having one of these, I can use various patterns of makeup,
I can do all kinds of makeup patterns with just this one,
For example, I'm going out for dinner tonight at a nice place, so I'll add a little glitter,
I'm going out for dinner tonight, so let's add a little glitter,
I love it so much.
I use it a lot in my daily life and at live performances.
I love it.
As expected of Kitagawa-san, from Depakos.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll go now.
Next, this one. I've been using it for a while,
It's a limited edition color called Ballerina Pop by Clinique.
It's a limited edition color, but it's not sold in Japan, and I wonder if it's available in Korea.
It's cute. It's so cute.
It's a white pink, and I usually add a bit more coral to it,
I usually add a little more coral to it and layer it with blush and it's really pretty.
Highly recommended.
It's so cute.
I love it, even if I can't pop it off.Maybe it's that I can't pop it, but I love it.
Ehhhhh.
What, some people like to do makeup and some like to collect?
Maybe if it's collecting, we're pretty much the same here.
We always talk about new products, like, "I heard this is coming out next month.
But are there people who like to do it, or are they good at it, like Ms. Oda? Sakura Oda, for example.
She said she likes to do it to others.
Oda-san also does a lot of makeup for the younger students.
Is that the last one?
Yes, that's it.
This is it.
Spicypi lame? Glitter? I got this as a birthday present from Rina-san.
Rina-san gave me this as a birthday present, and it has large particles of lame, so it's really cute.
I put it on here, and I also heard that it is good to put it under eyeliner for Hamare-chan, so I've been using it for a long time.
It's cute. I highly recommend it.
I have an image of Mei.
Lastly, I'll leave you with this.
I feel like I'm in the sky.
This is Amplitude's blush No. 02, and it really feels great,
This soft pink is my second one. I love it so much.
My face is not complete without it.
It's going to run out this year. I'm going to withdraw from the market, so I'm going to buy at least two more. I'm going to have to save up for two more,
It's pink from the inside, but it's like my skin,
It is really beautiful and makes my skin shiny, but it is not too shiny.
I love it.
Here is the last one for me.
Here it is. Makeup keeping powder. This is a powder from the famous spray type,
It's really good, and I really like the super-matte finish. I really like the super-matte look, like at a concert.
It's like it doesn't give any shine at all, so I really like the smoothness of this powder,
Even if you put it on top of it, the particles are very fine so it doesn't look dirty.
I highly recommend it.
That's all.
I introduced three products. What do you think?
So, we are going back to the shooting.
Bye bye. Thank you very much.